
TimeCreated            Id Msg                                                                                               
-----------            -- ---                                                                                               
7/25/2026 11:55:58 PM 566 The system session has transitioned from 183 to 185. Reason InputHid BootId: 68                   
7/25/2026 11:55:58 PM 507 The system is exiting Modern Standby Reason: Input Mouse.                                         
7/25/2026 3:30:48 AM  506 The system is entering Modern Standby Reason: Idle Timeout.                                       
7/25/2026 3:30:48 AM  566 The system session has transitioned from 182 to 183. Reason SessionUnlock BootId: 68              
7/25/2026 3:30:16 AM  566 The system session has transitioned from 180 to 182. Reason InputHid BootId: 68                   
7/25/2026 3:30:16 AM  507 The system is exiting Modern Standby Reason: Input Mouse.                                         
7/25/2026 3:16:30 AM  506 The system is entering Modern Standby Reason: Idle Timeout.                                       
7/25/2026 3:16:30 AM  566 The system session has transitioned from 179 to 180. Reason SessionUnlock BootId: 68              
7/25/2026 3:16:00 AM  566 The system session has transitioned from 177 to 179. Reason InputHid BootId: 68                   
7/25/2026 3:16:00 AM  507 The system is exiting Modern Standby Reason: Input Mouse.                                         
7/25/2026 3:15:41 AM  506 The system is entering Modern Standby Reason: Idle Timeout.                                       
7/25/2026 3:15:41 AM  566 The system session has transitioned from 176 to 177. Reason SessionUnlock BootId: 68              
7/25/2026 3:15:10 AM  566 The system session has transitioned from 174 to 176. Reason InputHid BootId: 68                   
7/25/2026 3:15:10 AM  507 The system is exiting Modern Standby Reason: Input Mouse.                                         
7/25/2026 3:14:15 AM  506 The system is entering Modern Standby Reason: Idle Timeout.                                       
7/25/2026 3:14:15 AM  566 The system session has transitioned from 173 to 174. Reason SessionUnlock BootId: 68              
7/25/2026 3:13:45 AM  566 The system session has transitioned from 171 to 173. Reason InputHid BootId: 68                   
7/25/2026 3:13:45 AM  507 The system is exiting Modern Standby Reason: Input Mouse.                                         
7/25/2026 3:11:01 AM  506 The system is entering Modern Standby Reason: Idle Timeout.                                       
7/25/2026 3:11:01 AM  566 The system session has transitioned from 170 to 171. Reason SessionUnlock BootId: 68              
7/25/2026 3:10:30 AM  566 The system session has transitioned from 168 to 170. Reason InputHid BootId: 68                   
7/25/2026 3:10:30 AM  507 The system is exiting Modern Standby Reason: Input Mouse.                                         
7/25/2026 2:43:04 AM  506 The system is entering Modern Standby Reason: Idle Timeout.                                       
7/25/2026 2:43:04 AM  566 The system session has transitioned from 167 to 168. Reason SessionUnlock BootId: 68              
7/25/2026 2:37:54 AM  566 The system session has transitioned from 166 to 167. Reason InputAccelerometer BootId: 68         
7/25/2026 2:37:54 AM  507 The system is exiting Modern Standby Reason: Input Keyboard.                                      
7/25/2026 2:37:35 AM  566 The system session has transitioned from 165 to 166. Reason PolicyChange BootId: 68               
7/25/2026 2:37:34 AM  506 The system is entering Modern Standby Reason: Lid.                                                
7/25/2026 2:37:34 AM  566 The system session has transitioned from 164 to 165. Reason PolicyChange BootId: 68               
7/25/2026 2:37:21 AM  566 The system session has transitioned from 162 to 164. Reason PolicyChange BootId: 68               
7/25/2026 2:37:21 AM  507 The system is exiting Modern Standby Reason: Lid.                                                 
7/25/2026 2:37:21 AM  506 The system is entering Modern Standby Reason: Lid.                                                
7/25/2026 2:37:21 AM  566 The system session has transitioned from 161 to 162. Reason PolicyChange BootId: 68               
7/25/2026 2:36:52 AM  566 The system session has transitioned from 159 to 161. Reason PolicyChange BootId: 68               
7/25/2026 2:36:52 AM  507 The system is exiting Modern Standby Reason: Lid.                                                 
7/25/2026 2:36:50 AM  506 The system is entering Modern Standby Reason: Sleep, Hibernate, or Shutdown.                      
7/25/2026 2:36:50 AM  566 The system session has transitioned from 158 to 159. Reason SxTransition BootId: 68               
7/25/2026 2:36:49 AM  105 Power source change.                                                                              
7/22/2026 4:52:25 AM  107 The system has resumed from sleep.                                                                
7/22/2026 4:52:19 AM   42 The system is entering sleep. Sleep Reason: Hibernate from Sleep - Standby Battery Budget Exceeded
7/22/2026 4:52:03 AM  566 The system session has transitioned from 157 to 158. Reason SxTransition BootId: 68               
7/22/2026 4:52:03 AM  507 The system is exiting Modern Standby Reason: Sleep, Hibernate, or Shutdown.                       
7/22/2026 4:52:03 AM  172 Connectivity state in standby: Connected, Reason: None                                            
7/22/2026 1:37:49 AM  172 Connectivity state in standby: Disconnected, Reason: Policy Setting                               
7/22/2026 1:37:44 AM  566 The system session has transitioned from 156 to 157. Reason 55 BootId: 68                         
7/22/2026 1:37:39 AM  172 Connectivity state in standby: Connected, Reason: None                                            
7/22/2026 1:37:39 AM  506 The system is entering Modern Standby Reason: Austerity Battery Drain Budget Exceeded.            
7/22/2026 1:37:39 AM  566 The system session has transitioned from 155 to 156. Reason 55 BootId: 68                         
7/22/2026 1:37:39 AM  507 The system is exiting Modern Standby Reason: Austerity Battery Drain Budget Exceeded.             
7/21/2026 10:31:33 PM 172 Connectivity state in standby: Disconnected, Reason: Adaptive Connected Standby                   
7/21/2026 10:31:27 PM 566 The system session has transitioned from 154 to 155. Reason InputMouse BootId: 68                 
7/21/2026 10:31:22 PM 506 The system is entering Modern Standby Reason: AC/DC Display Burst Suppressed.                     
7/21/2026 10:31:22 PM 566 The system session has transitioned from 153 to 154. Reason InputMouse BootId: 68                 
7/21/2026 10:31:22 PM 507 The system is exiting Modern Standby Reason: AC/DC Display Burst Suppressed.                      
7/21/2026 10:31:21 PM 105 Power source change.                                                                              
7/21/2026 9:49:05 PM  566 The system session has transitioned from 152 to 153. Reason PolicyChange BootId: 68               
7/21/2026 9:49:04 PM  506 The system is entering Modern Standby Reason: Lid.                                                
7/21/2026 9:49:04 PM  566 The system session has transitioned from 151 to 152. Reason PolicyChange BootId: 68               
7/21/2026 12:08:12 AM 566 The system session has transitioned from 149 to 151. Reason InputAccelerometer BootId: 68         
7/21/2026 12:08:12 AM 507 The system is exiting Modern Standby Reason: Input Keyboard.                                      


